mywarrantyrewards.com 2014-03-27

# Warranty Rewards Privacy Policy

                                    Warranty Rewards Privacy Policy
Our Commitment to Privacy
Our Privacy Policy has been developed as an extension of our commitment to combine quality products
and services with integrity in dealing with users. The Policy is designed to assist you in the understanding
of how we collect, use and protect the personal information provided to us.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our site, we collect two types of information: personal information you actively choose to
disclose (“Active Information”) and Use information collected, in a way not visible to you, on an
aggregate anonymous basis as you and other users browse our site (“Passive Information”).
1. Personally Identifiable Information
This refers to information that lets us know specifically about you i.e. profile information.
A. Registration
When you register to become an authorized reseller of our products or services, we will collect Personally
Identifiable Information (such as name, address, email address, and telephone number). This Personally
Identifiable Information is securely stored and may be accessed on our website. You are assigned an
identification number and select your own password – both are needed to enter the Site and to access your
Contact Information. Please safeguard your password in a secure location as we are not responsible for
breaches into the system when access is willingly provided.
B. Ordering
When you place an order for products or services, we collect Personally Identifiable Information (such as
name, contact and billing information, credit card, and other transactional information). We use this
information to deliver your order, process payment, and to communicate the status of your order.
C. Credit Card Storage
Credit card information collected at registration or for product orders is used only to process payment for
the transaction and, generally, is not retained on our Site. However, you may voluntarily elect to securely
store multiple credit cards to be used for product orders.
D. Surveys and Promotions
Occasionally, you may voluntarily provide Personally Identifiable Information to complete surveys and
questionnaires or to participate in user polls. We use this information to improve our products and
services and to ensure that we’re providing accurate disclosures. We may also use your Personally
Identifiable Information to provide you newsletters and other marketing information that coincide with
your preferences. You may customize your marketing preferences, or let us know if you do not wish to
receive any promotional materials, by adjusting your Subscriptions & Email options on the Site.

2. Aggregate Information
This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify you as a specific individual. Such information
would include the Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) of the website that referred you to our Site, your
Internet Protocol (“IP”) address (a number automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf
the web), your operating system and browser type, and any search terms that you enter on our Site. Our
web server aggregates this information in order to monitor the level of activity on our Site, evaluate its
effectiveness, and improve the content or our Site in order to make your visit an easy and enjoyable
experience.
We may collect, compile, store, publish, promote, report, or otherwise disclose or use any Aggregate
Information, provided that such information does not personally identify you. We do not correlate any
Personally Identifiable Information with the Aggregate Information that we collect on our Site. If we do
correlate any Aggregate Information to you, it will be protected like any other Personally Identifiable
Information under this Privacy Statement.
Active Information You Choose to Provide
In order to gain use of the site (become a “user”), we require you to disclose the following information:
Name, Address and Phone Number
We use secure socket layer (SSL) encryption to protect the transmission of the information you submit to
us when you use our secure online forms. The information you provide to us is stored securely.
Passive Information Collected
What is a Cookie?
Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to
access a site. They are small pieces of data stored by a user’s browser to simplify subsequent interactions
with the site. This makes it easier for a user to move from site to site and to complete transactions over the
Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
Our site utilizes cookies to collect information about how our site is used. Passive Information gathered
may include the date and time of visits, the site pages viewed, time spent at our site, the sites visited just
before and just after visiting our site. If you do not wish to transmit “cookie” information about yourself,
you may turn off the cookie function in your web browser.
Our site’s servers also automatically identify you computer by its Internet Protocol address, which is a
unique string of numbers that are assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. The IP
address may be used to address problems with our server or to gather broad demographic information
about our users. We passively collect your IP Address.
How Do We Use the Information Collected?
Broadly speaking, persons we employ directly, or as contractors or agents at our direction use Active
Information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing customer support and making
available other products or services we think might be of interest to our users. We may use the Active
Information or Passive Information you provide to contact you about various changes to our site, new
services, features or products we offer. If at any time you do not wish to receive such information, you
may “opt-out” of doing so by adjusting your email settings in the back office of the website.

We use Passive Information to gather information about our users and to enhance our site to make it
easier, faster and friendlier for users. Additionally, cookies help us better understand the usage pattern of
the people that visit our site, which helps us improve our services. Passive Information may result in your
viewing of particular advertising based on your user habits.
Your Information In Relation to Others We Link To
You might be able to access other websites through our site via hyperlinks. When you do so, you are
subjecting yourself to their privacy policies and data collection. Please read the privacy policies of those
sites to ensure you agree with the terms before using such sites.
Sharing Information with Advertisers or Other Third Parties
We may disclose anonymous information about user habits to advertisers on our site. The parties who
perform services for us (credit card processors, merchant bank, Internet Service Provider) may also have
access to your information in performing such services. Should we buy or sell assets of our company,
another company may need to review our company’s assets, which might include your information, to
make business decisions as to whether to acquire such assets.
Sharing Information with the Government or As Otherwise Required by Law
We may be required by subpoena, law or government agency to disclose both Active and Passive
Information you have provided to us.
How Do We Secure Active Information and Passive Information?
We secure your personal information submitted by you by using reasonable efforts to prevent
unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss of Active and Passive Information. Individual
postings on this site and other communications to our office via email or standard mail may not be secure
unless we advise you that security measures are in place prior to your submission of information.
Therefore, if you choose to communicate with us through these means, you are assuming the risk of doing
so and we respectfully request that you do not send or post sensitive information through these means.
Accessing and Correcting Your Information
We take reasonable measures to ensure that any Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our Site
is accurate, current, complete, and reliable for its intended use. If you wish to update or otherwise correct
Personally Identifiable Information provided to us, you may edit your information online.
Protecting Your Information
We acknowledge your trust and are committed to take reasonable steps to protect Personally Identifiable
Information provided from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. We employ physical, electronic, and
managerial processes to safeguard and secure your information.
It is your responsibility to safeguard the password you use to access our Site and to promptly advise us if
you ever suspect that your password has been compromised. We strongly encourage you to change your
password regularly to prevent unauthorized access. Because your identification number and password are
specific to you, you acknowledge sole responsibility for any and all use of our Site conducted with your
identification number and password.

Links to Other Websites
Links to third-party websites may be provided solely for your information and convenience or to provide
additional shopping for various other goods and services through our Merchant and Services Partners. If
you use these links, you will leave our Site. This Privacy Statement does not cover the information
practices of those websites nor do we control their content or privacy policies. We suggest that you
carefully review the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Children’s Privacy Protection
We take special care to protect the privacy needs of children and encourage parents to be an active
participant in their child’s online activities. Our Site does not target and is not intended for children under
the age of 18, and we will not knowingly collect Personally Identifiable Information from them. If we
discover personal data from a child through our site, we will eliminate that data. You may learn more
about protecting children’s privacy online by visiting:
http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec08.shtm
Changes to This Statement
Any updates or changes to the terms of this Privacy Statement will be posted on our Site and the date of
the newest version posted below. Please check back frequently, especially before you submit any
Personally Identifiable Information at our Site, to see if this Privacy Statement has changed. By using our
Site, you acknowledge acceptance of this Privacy Statement in effect at the time of use.
YOUR USE OF OUR SITE MEANS THAT YOU ACCEPT THE PRACTICES SET FORTH IN THIS
POLICY. YOUR CONTINUED USE INDICATES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE CHANGES.
